<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Computational Pathology Group</title><link href="https://diagnijmegen.github.io/website-pathology/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="https://diagnijmegen.github.io/website-pathology/feeds/all.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>https://diagnijmegen.github.io/website-pathology/</id><updated>2017-12-01T00:00:00+01:00</updated><entry><title>Camelyon16 published in JAMA</title><link href="https://diagnijmegen.github.io/website-pathology/news/camelyon16-published-in-jama/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-12-01T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2017-12-01T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>WebteamDIAG</name></author><id>tag:diagnijmegen.github.io,2017-12-01:/website-pathology/news/camelyon16-published-in-jama/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Diagnostic Image Analysis Group organized Camelyon16, the first medical image analysis challenge with whole slide digital pathology images in 2016. The competition was a great success, and several of the submitted software solutions outperformed human pathologists in the detection of lymph node metastases. The results of Camelyon16 were published …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;The Diagnostic Image Analysis Group organized Camelyon16, the first medical image analysis challenge with whole slide digital pathology images in 2016. The competition was a great success, and several of the submitted software solutions outperformed human pathologists in the detection of lymph node metastases. The results of Camelyon16 were published in JAMA and covered by the national Dutch television show Nieuwsuur.&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry><entry><title>NOS news article</title><link href="https://diagnijmegen.github.io/website-pathology/news/nos-news-article/" rel="alternate"></link><published>2017-03-04T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2017-03-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated><author><name>WebteamDIAG</name></author><id>tag:diagnijmegen.github.io,2017-03-04:/website-pathology/news/nos-news-article/</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;Jeroen van der Laak has contributed to a news article of the NOS about the success of a deep learning-based algorithm to automatically detect malignant lymph tissue in pathology slides. The algorithm, trained on data provided by the DIAG group, outperforms pathologists on this task. More info can be found …&lt;/p&gt;</summary><content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Jeroen van der Laak has contributed to a news article of the NOS about the success of a deep learning-based algorithm to automatically detect malignant lymph tissue in pathology slides. The algorithm, trained on data provided by the DIAG group, outperforms pathologists on this task. More info can be found on the Google research Blog and in the resulting paper.&lt;/p&gt;</content></entry></feed>